[
    {
      "question": "Yo practico _____.",
      "answer": "Baile",
      "options": ["Música", "Baile", "Nosotros", "Felizmente"]
    },
    {
      "question": "La _____ comienza.",
      "answer": "Celebración",
      "options": ["Cantar", "Baile", "Celebración", "Alegría"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Siento mucha _____.",
      "answer": "Alegría",
      "options": ["Divertido", "Música", "Ruidoso", "Alegría"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Escucho la _____.",
      "answer": "Música",
      "options": ["Cantar", "Baile", "Música", "Alegría"]
    },
    {
      "question": "La fiesta es _____.",
      "answer": "Divertido",
      "options": ["Nosotros", "Cantar", "Bailar", "Divertido"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Nos gusta _____.",
      "answer": "Bailar",
      "options": ["Bailar", "Baile", "Música", "Cantar"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Ellos _____ en la fiesta.",
      "answer": "Cantan",
      "options": ["Escuchan", "Celebran", "Cantan", "Bailan"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Ellos celebran _____.",
      "answer": "Felizmente",
      "options": ["Baile", "Felizmente", "Ruidoso", "Divertido"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Nosotros _____ juntos.",
      "answer": "Celebramos",
      "options": ["Bailamos", "Escuchamos", "Celebramos", "Cantamos"]
    },
    {
      "question": "La celebración es _____.",
      "answer": "Ruidoso",
      "options": ["Nosotros", "Felizmente", "Bailar", "Ruidoso"]
    }
  ]
  
